loopdesk.com 2018-06-03

# LoopDesk - FREE Online Business Networking Group

* * *

This policy describes LoopDesk's commitment to protecting your privacy and the personal information you provide on the LoopDesk Site.  The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. As this policy may change from time to time, please check back periodically. 

**Registration**  
When you visit the LoopDesk Site, you may provide us with two types of information: (1) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and, (2) Site use information collected by us on an aggregate basis as you and others browse the Site. 

_When you _register__ _on the Site_ , you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, company name, email address, telephone number, business address and any other personal or preference information that you wish to disclose.  Your email address will be your username and you will create a password and establish your privacy settings.  Your information and profile will be displayed to all members of the LoopDesk Site and may be featured in areas such as the Featured Members area or the Members You May Know area.  We may use your email address to send you notices of upgrades or changes to the Site, the Terms of Service or the Privacy Policy as well as new services, special offers and other communications.  All personal information you submit to the Site will be protected by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.  If you link to another site or sign up for an affiliate program or contest or answer an advertisement through the Site, you are submitting your personal information to that vendor.  Any personal information you volunteer to that vendor is subject to the terms and condition of that vendor’s privacy policy.

_When you _enter__ _the Site_ , we collect your browser type and IP address.  This information is gathered from all users of the Site and is used primarily to help diagnose and fix any technical problems and to recognize you when you return to the Site (we keep track of your email address and password when you are signed in so you don’t have to re-sign in every time you visit a new page on the Site).  In addition, we use the information to measure traffic and visiting patterns on the Site and on other websites on the Internet.  We may also compile statistics and other data about our customers on an aggregate basis, and may share such aggregate data with selected third parties.  In addition, we store certain information from your browser using “cookies.”  A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer tied to information about you. Some third-party advertisers may also use cookies when their ads are viewed on the Site.  These cookies help us provide you with customized content.  We do not use cookies to collect private information about you.  We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our Site.  If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can turn them off using your browser's settings **.   **

**Invitations**  
LoopDesk invites you to invite your business colleagues to join you on the Site, provided such colleagues comply with our Eligibility Requirements found in our **[Terms of Service](http://www.loopdesk.com/help_tos.php)**.  If you choose to tell a business colleague about the Site, we will ask you for your business colleague’s name and email address. We will automatically send your business colleague a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site.  We do not save or share your business colleague’s email address; we only use it for this one time mailing. Please note that LoopDesk opposes the practice of sending unsolicited commercial emails, also known as "spam". Therefore, we request that you ask us to invite only people known by you who may be interested in the Site. If someone asks you not to invite them, please respect their request. 

**Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties**  
LoopDesk can (and you hereby authorize us to) release any personally identifiable information about you when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with law, enforce or apply the terms of the LoopDesk Terms of Service, enforce other LoopDesk rights, or protect the rights, property or safety of LoopDesk, the Site, or other users.  Further, as permitted by applicable law, LoopDesk can (and you hereby authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email and any other information you have provided to us in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity whenever LoopDesk, in its sole discretion, believes necessary or appropriate. In the event LoopDesk merges with or acquires another company, or sells all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information may be among assets transferred.  In addition, we may share information about you with third parties as necessary to complete a transaction requested by you and we may share information about you with our business partners, affiliates or other third parties. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire to use the Site, you may correct, update, or delete the information by accessing the member account page. 

**Links**  
The Site may contain links to other websites. We provide these links for your convenience, but we do not review, control or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by others. We are not responsible for the content or performance of these sites or for your use of them. Your use of other websites is subject to the terms and conditions of those websites, including the privacy policies of those websites. 

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties**  
**Except for** compiling statistics and other data about our customers on an aggregate basis, we do not provide your personal information to any third party marketers without your permission.  We only share your personal information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.  Please keep in mind that Loop Desk is a business networking service, so the information you provide will be available to all other users of the LoopDesk Site.

**Third Party Advertising**  
**Advertisements that appear on the LoopDesk site may be either delivered by LoopDesk or other third party advertising delivery services.   These third party services may download cookies to your computer or use other technologies to measure the advertising effectiveness or personalize advertisements to you.  Anytime you click on an advertisement you are leaving the LoopDesk Site and going to a third party’s site.  LoopDesk has no control once you leave its Site and move to an advertiser’s site.  This Privacy Policy covers the use of the LoopDesk Site, not any site you may link to through an advertisement.**

**Security   **  
We take appropriate precautions to protect our users’ information.  Your access to the Site is password-protected so that only you and authorized LoopDesk employees have access to your account.  In order to maintain this protection, do not give your password to anyone.  If you share a computer, be sure to sign off the Site and close the browser window before someone else logs on.  This will help protect your information at public terminals.  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure.  As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or other Site users; your use of the Site is of your own risk.

**Export of Data**  
Recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all laws and rules regarding online conduct and privacy, as well as content. Specifically, but not as a limitation, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding transmission of technical and personal data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.

**Additional Information**  
Please [**click here**](http://www.loopdesk.com/help_contact.php) if you have questions about this Privacy Policy or the LoopDesk Site.

|
